ripetv.com 2009-09-18

# Privacy Policy - Ripe TV

### Ripe Digital Entertainment's Privacy Policy

Ripe Digital Entertainment ("Ripe") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of all visitors to its Site (defined below). Ripe recognizes the potential of technology to help you communicate with us via our website and through e-mail and we would like to use this technology over time to develop a relationship with you. The privacy policy below details the measures taken by Ripe to protect your privacy in connection with your use of www.ripe.tv and other sites hereafter owned or operated by Ripe (collectively, "Site"). Please read the following to learn more about Ripe's privacy policy. 

This privacy policy is incorporated into and is subject to Ripe's Terms of Use. If you do not agree to the terms of this privacy policy or the Terms of Use, please do not provide Ripe with any information and do not use the Site. Ripe reserves the right to modify the privacy policy at anytime in its sole discretion. Your continued use of the Site after the privacy policy has been modified will signify your acceptance of the changes for information gathered after the date of the change. 

####  I. Overview 

This policy statement discloses Ripe's privacy practices including the notification of: 

A. Personal information ("PI") collected through the Site; B. Intended usage of this PI; C. Choices available regarding opt-in/opt-out, data collection, use and distribution of the information; 

D. Security measures to protect the loss or misuse of information under Ripe's control; and E. How to maintain the accuracy of your information. 

####  II. General Information 

In general, you may visit the Site and access information while not revealing any individual user information other than Technology Related Information (defined below). If you upload content to this Site, the content will be governed by the Terms of Use, the Material Submission License Agreement and a submission license agreement, if any, and any other terms or conditions on the upload pages. The types of individual user information collected in the registration process may include your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, other contact information, and/or other PI volunteered by you. 

####  III. Information Collection and Use 

Ripe collects PI when you register with Ripe, when you visit certain Ripe pages and when you deliver communications or content to the Site. Ripe may combine information about you that Ripe has with information we obtain from business associates or otherwise. Without limitation, information collected, including PI, may be used by Ripe for internal research purposes, marketing, promotions and public relations, subject only to the terms of Ripe's privacy policy. 

Ripe will not disclose, transfer, sell or otherwise communicate your PI to any third party, other than Ripe's parent, subsidiaries, affiliates, successors, assigns, and licensees and each of their officers, directors, employees and vendors and contractors operating under confidentiality agreements and subject to Ripe's privacy policy, unless you give Ripe permission to do so, except as set forth in this privacy policy. Notwithstanding the foregoing or anything to the contrary, Ripe may disclose any information you provide if required to do so by law or pursuant to a request by law enforcement or if Ripe has a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with the law or with the legal process; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Ripe or third parties; or (c) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety or legal rights ("Mandatory Disclosures"). Ripe may buy or sell assets or change its name or form of entity, and, depending upon the transaction, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets in which case Ripe reserves the right to sell or transfer your PI. Ripe will notify you before PI about you becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

To help administer the Site, Ripe does collect technology-related information. "Technology-Related Information" may include , but is not limited to the following: source IP address, domain name, date and time visited and visited pages. "Cookies" are bits of electronic information that a website can transfer to a visitor's hard drive to help keep records of your visit to the site. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many major websites use them. Your browser has options to accept, reject or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. Ripe uses cookies for many purposes such as to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Ripe also uses cookies to deliver content (which may include third party advertisements) specific to your interests. Ripe may set and access Ripe "cookies" on your computer. Ripe lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Ripe's cookies. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not Ripe's. Ripe has no control over the information collected from or about you by any third party after you have left the Site. By clicking on links to other websites, advertisers and other third parties, you are leaving the Site. Once you have left the Site, Ripe does not control the data collection and privacy practices, or other activities, of any third party linked to this Site and Ripe assumes no liability and is not responsible for any practices of such third party websites. 

####  IV. Consent/Opt-In/Modifying PI 

Ripe may receive and consider requests from third parties to contact you, but Ripe will not give that third party any PI unless Ripe has obtained your consent. You may give this consent to having your information shared with third parties when you register by choosing to opt-in. Additionally, Ripe provides you the opportunity to be sent newsletters and information about programming, promotional events, marketing events and opportunities to participate in research studies. If you would like to exercise your right under the CAN SPAM Act to not receive future e-mail correspondence from Ripe, except with respect to your prior financial transactions or communications, regarding Mandatory Disclosures or as otherwise required by law, you may do so by using a link provided at the bottom of these communications. You can also send us an email at info@ripe.tv for any opt-out or opt-in purpose. 

####  V. Security 

Ripe has implemented security measures to protect PI collected on our Site against loss, misuse or alteration. However, the Internet is an open system and technology and human operators are not infallible. Accordingly, Ripe cannot and does not guarantee that the individual user information you have transmitted, including PI, will not be intercepted by others and/or decrypted or accidentally disclosed. Ripe cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted over the Internet, and Ripe accepts no liability for any unintentional disclosure. 

####  VI. Modifications to the Privacy Policy 

Ripe's privacy policy may change from time to time at its sole discretion. If Ripe decides to make any material changes, Ripe will post these changes on the Site. If, at any point, Ripe decides to use PI in a manner different than what was stated at the time it was collected, Ripe will notify users of this change via e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not Ripe can use their information in this different manner. Ripe will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected unless you agree otherwise. 

####  VII. Note to Parents of Minors 

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), Ripe is a general audience site and does not intend to collect any PI from children under 18 years of age, unless Ripe believes such collection to be permitted by law. The Site targets an audience that is 18 years of age or older and some content may not be appropriate for all ages. Parental supervision is recommended. If you are the pa rent or guardian of a child under 18 and believe that he or she has disclosed PI to Ripe, please contact info@ripe.tv. Upon request, the parent or guardian of a child under the age of 18 may review and request the deletion of such child's PI, as well as refuse to permit the further collection or use of such PI. 

Still have Questions? If you have any questions, or believe Ripe is not adhering to its posted privacy policy, you should contact Ripe's privacy manager by email at [info@ripe.tv](mailto:info@ripe.tv) (Last Modified: April 10, 2008)
